<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Tech &#8211; justinmcintyre.com</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 04:22:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Started Learning Vim</title>
		<link>./../../../started-learning-vim/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 04:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Tech]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=24</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Why did I start learning Vim? It started as a simple curiosity. A few days ago, Vim was only a program that forced me to reboot my computer when I first started exploring the Linux OS. Initially, I wasn't sure how Vim could enable a writer to be noticeably more capable at the keyboard. I [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Why did I start learning Vim?</h1>
<p>It started as a simple curiosity.<br />
A few days ago, Vim was only a program that forced me to reboot my computer when I first started exploring the Linux OS.</p>
<p>Initially, I wasn't sure how Vim could enable a writer to be noticeably more capable at the keyboard. I understood that using your mouse was inefficient, but I still didn't understand how Vim was more efficient.</p>
<p>I dabbled a little bit; learned how to use &quot;HJKL&quot; to move the cursor, but I wasn't impressed. So once again, I put the idea of learning aside.</p>
<h2>I've learned a lot since</h2>
<p>Since then, my abilities as a developer have surpassed my initial ambitions; but I haven't looked back at Vim till recently.</p>
<p>Vim came back into my consciousness when I came across a Reddit forum of Vim enthusiasts explaining how the text editor allowed them to increase their output at the keyboard.</p>
<p>I remained skeptical, reminded of my initial experiences using Vim<br />
until I read this article. I realized that Vim didn't have one specific feature that allowed users to become more efficient. Instead, it's the ridiculous amount of ways a skilled Vim user can edit text that gave Vim its merit ( these features even include Regular Search Expressions! ).</p>
<p>Quickly, I concluded that Vim was worth learning, but I'd have to go in cold turkey. Learning the workflow half-ass would be a slow, painful and inefficient process.</p>
<h2>The results to date</h2>
<p>Two weeks in, I love it! I'm not too sure if I'm faster, but I think I've at least matched my previous output. On top of that, I've found enjoyment in something I didn't previously have. Typing used to be a means to an end, but Vim made it a fun activity.</p>
<p>I imagine beginning calligraphists feel something similar.</p>
<p>FYI this article was written and edited using the Vim plugin in VScode, and I imagine that subsequent articles will as well.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
